A Guide to the Henry G. Kunkel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA273
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Visual Materials, 1946-1983; 7
  - Slides, 7.3
    - 1619: RFc andy glob, small amt & Macro andy glob, small amt., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1620: RFc and alb. & Macro and alb., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1629: New RF(d) and Serum(bot); Macro and Serum (top), Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1630: RF(d) alone; Macro alone, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1638: RF(d) and 75 (Polio) repeat, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1638: RF(d) and 75 (Polio) repeat, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1671-1 &1671-2: Euglob. alone in 20% NaCl and plate 1 of 1671.2 RF(f) alone, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1671-1 &1671-2: Euglob. alone in 20% NaCl and plate 1 of 1671.2 RF(f) alone, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1672: L RF(f) and Serum; IL Serum alone, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1673: L RF(f) and Polio v; IL RF(f) alone, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1761: Bemis serum and Polio v, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1768: Bemis 63ø v prec. In glyc.-HCl Buffer, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1771, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1790: Serum Hutchinson: 1/4, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1791: Serum Hutchinson and v glob- (fair) to be repealed: 1/4, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1795: Hutchinson: 1,2,3 Cryoglob.; 4,5,6 Euglob of Cryoglob, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1797: Fresh Serum-Hutchinson, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1798: Hutchinson Euglob-top and 5% NaCI; Bet and Acid pH 3, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1799: Hutchinson-ice box; Hutchinson-deep freeze, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1800: Hutchinson Cryoeuglob, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1809: Hutchinson (New prepan)-Dr. Tomasi, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1813 & 1810: Serum-Hutchinson, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1813 & 1810: Serum-Hutchinson, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1818: Serum R Denison (Dr. Bland) - def. 225 pak.- v slight interned, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1837: Serum Hutchinson - orig. unfrozen, 1/1, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1848: Bemis Protein Isolated by Cryo and Electro-8 Intervals, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1870: Hutchinson Serum: I. & Murphy Rh Factor; II. And Kl 009 Rh non-reactor, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1870: Hutchinson Serum: I. & MurphyRh Factor; II. And Kl009 Rh non-reactor, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1870: Hutchinson Serum: I. & Murphy Rh Factor; II. And Kl 009 Rh non-reactor, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1871: Hutchinson Serum: I. & Murphy, reactor Rh, .07 Hutch. to .14 serum; II. & K1009 non-reactor, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1871: Hutchinson Serum: I. & Murphy, reactor Rh, .07 Hutch. to .14 serum; II. & K1009 non-reactor, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1878: Serum of Dr. Epstein- young girl, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1878: Serum of Dr. Epstein- young girl, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1882: Hutchinson Serum- still lower core: I. & Murphy (reactor); II. & K1009 (non-reactor), Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1882: Hutchinson Serum- still lower core: I. & Murphy (reactor); II. & K1009 (non-reactor), Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1994: Futz Serum- Macroglobulin, Cornell, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2015: Macro Futz isol., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2019: Macro Futz dissoc. And Jodoac., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2020: Macro Futz reassoc., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2032: Benua SH #3 and Lutz SH #3- reassoc. with dialysis. Exp. 3, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2158/2158-2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2158, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2158, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2158, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2346: Scott (Texas), 111, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2354: Browuell Texas - illegible undissolved, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2354: Browuell Texas - illegible undissolved, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2354: Browuell Texas - illegible undissolved, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2355: 1/4 Myrtll Scott Texas: RA Macro, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2355: 1/4 Myrtll Scott Texas: RA Macro, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2355: 1/4 Myrtll Scott Texas: RA Macro, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2357: B2, Dr. Pernis-RA Macro, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2357: B2, Dr. Pernis-RA Macro, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2357: B2, Dr. Pernis-RA Macro, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2510: O'Dell 195, prepared 1963 December 9, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2516: std. Donnellan 195 from G208 pH 4.0 wedge: Donnellan 195 often Hg Repair, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2519: Wedge Cell, Donnellan R.F. reduced and blocked, 1963 December 9, & Std. Cell, Donnellan R.F. reduced and re-associated, 1963 December 9, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2520: Wedge-O'Dell 195 Reduced and blocked, 1963 December 14 & Sdt. O'Dell 195 Reduced, re-associated, 1963 December 14, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2538: O'Dell after peu., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2543: O'Dell Serum and Fm II 2513, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2543: O'Dell Serum and Fm II 2513, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2656: Grodnolilgy, col. Agglut.- Dr. Jaffe, 1964 December 8; Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2656: Grodnolilgy, col. Agglut.- Dr. Jaffe, 1964 December 8; Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2656: Grodnolilgy, col. Agglut.- Dr. Jaffe, 1964 December 8; Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2656: Grodnolilgy, col. Agglut.- Dr. Jaffe, 1964 December 8; Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2803: Zuntz serum, 1:1 illegible, 1965 December 19; Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2840: Illegible yA #1, #2: 50, 1965 February 9; Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2844: Illegible, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2844: Illegible, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2846: Illegible, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2846: Illegible, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2928: Perrtra Black (First and Second), 1965 May 28; Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 2928: Perrtra Black (First and Second), 1965 May 28; Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 3834: Quintana Ser., 1:2, 1970 November 5; Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - E690: XXII Chas. Wasserman: RA Whole Serum, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - E690: XXII Chas. Wasserman: RA Whole Serum, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - E1162: Extra Intenned Peak- illegible Macroglobulin: E. Rose, Mt. Sinai, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson: Photo, Miscellaneous, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson: Photo, Miscellaneous, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson: Photo, Miscellaneous, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson Sera: I. Old Serum, II. Dr. Tom- frozen ser.- all 195 Unnumbered glass slide, undated; Fragile. Glass. (2 slides). (Box 95)
    - Unnumbered shattered glass slide, Untitled, undated; Fragile. Glass. (5 slides) (Box 95)
    - 920: I.Macroglob., Samuels; 2. 175- Rose, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 924: Amy lord, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1160: RA ppt., EP, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1160: RA ppt., EP, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1160: RA ppt., EP, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1160: RA ppt., EP, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1160: RA ppt., EP, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1160: RA ppt., EP, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1293-1: Solid yglob Eluate (Petty Ser.); 13:II-acid Ph 3.0, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1361: MG ñShapiro (Lee) (-) Finhen illegible: Corlay-Lee-Weisman, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1361: MG ñShapiro (Lee) (-) Finhen illegible: Corlay-Lee-Weisman, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1560 (a & b) and 1564 (poor): I. Isol. RF (a); Fuo illegible- 6. and Isol. RF (b): 1564-Badler and Isol. RF, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1560 (a & b) and 1564 (poor): I. Isol. RF (a); Fuo illegible- 6. and Isol. RF (b): 1564-Badler and Isol. RF, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1613: (1-4) La Pierrie; (5-6) New R. Fiet Stock Norm 13a34- no def. doubling, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1615: RF (c) alone; Macro alone, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1631: RF(d) and 75 (1/5 polis); 1633: +75 less, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1631: RF(d) and 75 (1/5 polis); 1633: +75 less, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1634: RF(d) and Rabb. y glob.; Macro and Rabb. y glob., Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1690-1 and 2: I. McCurdy Serum; II. Donnellan Serum-long run, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1690-1 and 2: I. McCurdy Serum; II. Donnellan Serum-long run, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1859: I. Rheum. F. (I) and Rosenfield, react; II. +K1009, no react.: Too little (No controls available), Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1861: Illegible for 1859; I. Rosenfield Serum; II. K-1009, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1872: I. Bemis orig. pure; Rheum. F. (J), Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1873: I. K1009 and RhF (J)- non-react (rh); II. K1009 and Bemis, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1874: I. Murphy and RhF(J) react (rh); II. 2722 and RhF(J) non-react, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 1875: I. Murphy and RhF(J)-.1 cc; II. 2722 and RhF(J), Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2018: Macro Futz, Pepsin tr., Fragile. Glass. (2 slides). (Box 96)
    - 2088: Serum Pierra (Dr. Peunis)- H-Rheum. F., Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2099: Pierra and yglob, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2099: Pierra and yglob, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2192: Pierra Euglob 7.5 b, Fragile. Glass. (2 slides). (Box 96)
    - 2231: Rans Macro, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2400, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2548: O'Dell SHand MeA: I. Fr II and MeA; II. Fr II, Fragile. Glass. (2 slides). (Box 96)
    - 2509: Roy peabs Dr. Alba, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2792: Chart yM, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2797: Illegible, 1:1, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2797: Illegible, 1:1, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2797: Illegible, 1:1, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2814: Illegible Serum, 1965 February; Fragile. Glass. (2 slides.) (Box 96)
    - 2835: Mehr yA- C200 0.16, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - 2837: Mehr yA for illegible, Fragile. Glass. (2 slides.) (Box 96)
    - 2847: Illegible, Fragile. Glass. (2 slides). (Box 96)
    - 3834, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - E1553: Fuo Serum- 1 Vol. and Rheum. Isol. Macro, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - E1554: Holman- 1 Vol. and Rheum. Isol. Macro, Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - Clegg- Cold Agg., Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - Un-numbered slide, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - Un-numbered slide, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 96)
    - Untitled, undated; Fragile. Glass. (5 slides, 8"x 12") (Box 97)
- Reprints, 1943-1984; 8
  Series 8: Reprints is arranged in the following subseries: Sub-series 1: Kunkel and Associates. Sub-series 2: Annotated Reprints by Others.
  - Kunkel and Associates, 8.1
    - 1943-1946 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - 1947 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - 1948 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - 1949 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - 1950 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - 1951 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - 1951-1962 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - 1951-1962 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - 1952 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - 1953 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - 1954 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - 1955 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - 1956 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - 1957 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - 1958 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - 1959 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - 1960 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - 1961 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - 1962 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - 1963 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - 1963-1967 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - 1963-1967 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - 1964 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - 1965 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Annals of the New York Academy of Sciences - Vol. 124, 1965 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - 1966 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - 1967 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - 1968 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - 1968-1970 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - 1968-1970 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - 1969 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Annals of the New York Academy of Sciences - Vol. 168, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - 1970 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - 1970-1973 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - 1970-1973 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - 1971 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - 1972 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - 1973 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - 1974 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - 1974-1977 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - 1974-1977 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - 1975 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - 1976 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - 1977 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - 1978 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - 1978-1983 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - 1978-1983 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - 1979 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - 1980 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - 1981 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - 1982 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - 1983 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - 1984 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Abstract - "Alterations in Estrogen Metabolism in Systemic Lupus Erythematosus,": Robert G. Labita, Henry G. Kunkel, and Jack Fishman, 1979 May/June (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Abstract - "Ia+ T Cells in Patients with Rheumatoid Arthritis": David T.Y. Yu, Robert J. Winchester, Henry G. Kunkel, et al., 1980 May (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - "Alterations of Estrogen Metabolism in Systemic Lupus Erythematosus": Robert G. Labita and H.G. Kunkel, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - "An Analysis of the Effect of Fat in the Diet on Recovery in Infectious Hepatitis": H.G. Kunkel, Charles Hoagland, et al., 1946 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - "Anti -Immunoglobulins and Their Idiotypes - Are They Part of the Immune Network?": H.G. Kunkel, David N. Posnett and Benvenuto Pernis, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - "Association of Three Interrelated Histocompatability Determinants with Susceptability to Rheumatoid Arthritis": Allan Gibofsky, Henry G. Kunkel, et al., May/June 1978 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - "Autoantibodies and Disease": Advances in Immunology: H.G. Kunkel and E.M. Tam, 1964 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - "Biological Properties of 16 a -Hydroxyestrone. Implications in Estrogen Physiology and in the Pathology of Cirrhosis and Systemic Lupus Erythematosus": Fishman and Martucci, undated (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Chapter 6 - "Zone Electrophoresis in Various Types of Supporting Media": Henry G. Kunkel and Rodes Trautman, undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Cochrane -Abq. Atb. Complexes: J.U. Pruss: JEM, undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - "Determination of 16 Alpha Hydroxyestrone by RIA in Systemic Lupus Erythematosus": H.G. Kunkel, et al., undated (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - "Differentiation Antigens Associated with Hairy Cell Leukemia": David N. Posnett and Charles C. Marboe, undated (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Edelman, Gerald, 1966, 1969 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - "Estrogen Metabolism in Systemic Lupus Erythematosus -Patients and Family Members": H.G. Kunkel, et al., undated (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - "Familial SLE in Males": H.G. Kunkel, et al., undated (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - "Final Draft Report": Meeting ofinvestigators on Primary Immune Deficiencies: Geneva: some pages missing, 1970 June 8-13 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - y Globulin, 1964-1965 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - "Genetic Markers of Human Immunoglobulins": Series Haematologica: Jacob B. Natvig and H.G. Kunkel, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Genetics, 1961-1966 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Genetics Papers, 1963-1967 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Gottlieb, Alice Bendix: Thesis, 1979 April (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - "Human Anti-y-Globulin Antibodies Specific for yG Heavy Chain Subclasses": Natvig, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - "Human Dendritic Cells -Major Stimulators of the Autologous and Allogeneic Mixed Leukocyte Reactions": Mary Kuntz Crow and H.G. Kunkel, undated (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - "Human Immunoglobulins -Classes, Subclasses, Genetic Variants, and Idiotypes": Natvig and Kunkel, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - "Hypoimmunoglobulinemia with Normal T -Cell Function in Female Siblings": Thomas Hoffinan, et al., 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - "Identification, Enumeration, and Isolation of B and T Lymphocytes from Human Peripheral Blood": Scandinavian Journal of Immunology, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - "Idiotype -like Molecules on Cells of a Human T -Cell Leukemia": H.G. Kunkel, et al., undated (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - "Immunochemical Studies on Blood Groups": Ten Feizi and Elvin A. Kabat: photocopy., 1972 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - "The Immunochemistry of Peptidoglycan": K.H. Schleifer and R.M. Krause:, 1971 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - "Immunofluorescent Localization of Double -Stranded RNA in Reovirus-Infected Cells": Samuel C. Silverstein and Peter H. Schur, 1970 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - "Immunological Aspects of Renal Disease": Kidney International: H.G. Kunkel and Frank J. Dixon, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - "Immunologic Aspects of Rheumatoid Arthritis": Conference on Rheumatoid Arthritis: Journal of Chronic Diseases, 1959 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - "The Immunology of Rheumatoid Diseases": Clinical Symposia: David Koffler, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - "The Immunopathology of SLE": Hospital Practice, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - "Increased Oxidation of Testosterone in Systemic Lupus Erythematosus": Robert G. Lahita, H.G. Kunkel, and H. Leon Bradlow (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - "The Inheritance ofindividual Antigenic Specificities of Rabbit Antibodies to Streptococcal Carbohydrates": Klaus Eichmann and Thomas J. Kindt, 1971 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - International Union of lmmunological Societies (IUIS) Report, 1974 July-1975 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - "Isolation of a Thermolabile Serum Protein which Precipitates y-Globulin Aggregates and Participates in Immune Hemolysis": Proceedings of the Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine: H.G. Kunkel and H.J. Miiller - Eberhard, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - J.F. Heremans, 1960-1961 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Kunkel Associates, 1946-1979 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Kunkel Associates, 1946-1979 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Kunkel Associates, 1964-1967 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Meeting Report - "Meeting Report of the Second International Workshop on Primary Immunodeficiency Diseases in Man", 1974 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - "Method for Direct Detection of Lymphocyte Binding of Aggregated y-Globulin" (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Kunkel Reprints, 1951, 1966, 1975-1985 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Reprints, 1935-1972 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Reprints, 1946-1969 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Monoclonal Antibodies:, undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - A Monoclonal IgG Protein with Antibody-Like Activity for Transferrin and with K Chains of an Unusual Molecular Size: P. Wernet, et al., 1974 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Mostov, Keith E., 1980, 1982-1983 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - A New Nonspecific Laboratory Test for the Demonstration of Specificity in Certain Nonspecific Diseases, Including Diseases of the Pacific, Specifically: Lewis Thomas, Lt. Commander, 1944 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Nucleoprotein Papers, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - PCA Passive Cutaneous Anaphylaxis, 1958-1960 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Pre-B Cells and Other Possible Precursor Lymphoid Cell Lines Derived from Patients with X-Linked Agammaglobulinemia: H.G. Kunkel, et al.., undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Protein Serum, 1963 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Scandinavian Journal of Immunology: Vol. 5, No. 6/7, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - SLE and GN Ref./Anti -DNA, 1964-1967 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - SLE - JEM Paper (with gallery proofs), 1967 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - SLE paper, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Soluble Suppressor Factors in Patients with Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome -Elaboration In Vitro by T Lymphocyte-Adherent Cell Interactions: Jeffrey Laurence, Alice B. Gottlieb, and H.G. Kunkel, undated (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - "Surface Immunoglobulins on B Lymphocytes": Shu Man Fu, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - "Surface Markers of Human Lymphocytes": H.G. Kunkel: Behring Institute Mitteilungen - Immunochemical Analysis of Various Biological Structures, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - "T -Cell Dependent and T -Cell Independent Activation of Human B Lymphocytes. Some Applications for the Study of Disease": N. Chiorazzi, undated (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - "Twenty -Four Year Old Woman with Arthritis, Skin Rash, Fever, and Anemia": Henry G. Kunkel and Robert E. Scully: The New England Journal of Medicine, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - "Two Types of !a -Positive T Cells. Synthesis and Exchange of Ia Antigens": D.T.Y. Yu, J.M. McCune, S.M. Fu, R.J. Winchester, H.G. Kunkel: The Journal of Experimental Medicine, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - "Ultra -Centrifugation Separation of Rheumatoid Ganuna Globulin": Serological Reactions of Rheumatoid Arthritis, 1957 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - World Health Organization (WHO) Reports, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - "Zone Electrophoresis": H.G. Kunkel: Biochemical Analysis, 1953 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - "Zone Electrophoresis in Various Types of Supporting Media": H.G. Kunkel and Rodes Trautman, undated (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Annotated Reprints by Others, 8.2
    - "Action des Detergents sur une (3 - Lipoproteine Isolee du Serum Hurnain": Marise Ayrault -Jarrier, 1959 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Agglutinins, Iso. -Rh., 1951-1976 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Alexander G. Bearn, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - "Allergy and Immuno-AIIergic Histiology": Lino Businco, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Antibodies, 1948-1962 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Antibodies (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Antibodies (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - 1 "Antibodies Directed Against Ribosomal Protein Determinants in the Sera of Patients with Connective Tissue Diseases": Julian Gordon, et al., 1981 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Antibody Isolation: Stratis Avrameas and Therese Ternynck, undated (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - B. Berggiird: "Memorial to Professor Ingemar Berggiird": The Scandinavian Journal of Clinical and Laboratory Investigation, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - "Bence Jones Proteins and Light Chains of lmmunoglobulins": Alan Solomon, Bias Frangione, and Edward C. Franklin, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Bona: "Immune Response to Levan", 1978 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Calmodulin, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - "Characterization oflgG Complexes in Eluates from Rheumatoid Tissue": Natvig, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Clinical and CLIM Immunology, 1960-1982 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - "Cionotypic Structures Involved in Antigen Specific Human T Cell Function?Relationship to the T3 Molecular Complex": Stefan C. Meuer, et al., undated (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Cold Agglutinins, 1966-1973 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - "Combination of Insulin Chains on an Anti-insulin Antibody - Sepharose Column": Mechthild Klotz and Bernd Gutte, 1976 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - "Complement -Fixing Properties of Pepsin -Treated Rabbit and Sheep Antibodies": Peter H. Schur and Elmer L. Becker, 1963 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - "Complete Amino Acid Sequence of a Mouse Immunoglobulin a-chain (MOPC 511)": Elizabeth A. Robinson and Ettore Appella, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - "Conformational Deviation in Immunoglobulins Related to Immune Complex Formation in Rheumatoid Sera": Michael Uesson, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - "Deoxyribonuclease Immobilized on the Erythrocytes": T. Kitao, Y. Kitao, and K. Hittori, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - "Discrete Gammaglobulin (M -) Components in Serum - Clinical Study of 150 Subjects without Myelomatosis": Jan Hallen, 1966 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - "The Distribution and Ultrastructure of the KurloffCell in the Guinea Pig: P.A. Revell, B. Vernon -Roberts, and A. Gray, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - "Etude Immunochimique de 130 Cryoglobulines Humaines": M. Klein, F. Danon, et al., 1972 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - "Expression of B and T-Cell Markers on Cultured Human Lymphoid WI -L2 Cells. Characteristics of the T-Cell Receptors": M.A. Pellegrino and S. Ferrone, undated (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Gamma Globulin: "Structure of Antibody Molecules": S. Cohen and C. Milstein, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - "HL -A and Disease Associations, A Survey": Arne Svejgaard, et al., undated (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - "How to Study Antigens by Means of Immunodiffusion and Immunoelectrophoresis": Thesis by Richard LaFond (Wesleyan University), 1968 October 28 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - "I alkylating agents", undated (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - Immune Complexes, 1979, undated (Box 108, Folder 24)